# **IBRAHIM ABDURRAHEEM**

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Freelance Web Developer with over 3 years of experience in frontend web development, I am driven and enthusiastic about getting into your esteemed university. diligent and motivated, with aspirations of succeeding in your prestigious university. Dedicated to putting forth a lot of effort and helping my community, peers, and school

### **WORK HISTORY**

### Web developer Mentor, 12/2022 to Current Remote - Ilorin

Teach mentees how to build simple web page with html and CSS.

Show mentees how to use Google to solve simple coding errors.

Give mentees links to the basic extensions that will make web development easier.

Assign assignment to mentees to improve their self development in coding .

# Web Developer Intern, 09/2022 to Current

#### Chingu - Remote

Developed using CSS, HTML, jQuery and JavaScripts to boost functionality and user experience on web pages.

Edit existing Codes to improve browser compatibility and mobile responsiveness

# Web Developer Intern, 09/2022 to Current RadicalX - Remote

Improved website navigation with clear and intuitive user experience.

Created custom websites by harnessing HTML, CSS and JavaScript skills.

Designed web pages to enhance branding and navigation.

Boosted website performance and stability through planned maintenance and targeted troubleshooting

# Frontend developer, 12/2019 to Current

#### Freelance

Meeting with the prospective clients to review website, and create certain features for existing websites.

Designing, coding a new website for the project using CSS, HTML javascript.

Built, designed and maintained the website for Oakream LLC using CSS, HTML and javascript.

Designing and implementing the front-end using HTML5, CSS3.

Built custom websites using Bootstrap and Word Press, including custom plug-ins and filters.

Build Shopify website and integrated it with several payment processorprocessor

# IT support specialist, 07/2018 to 10/2019 Network Operations Centre - Ilorin, Kwara

Deployment of Point-To-Point radio network to staff at GRA Quarters, Ilorin.

Installation, operation, and maintenance of network operations equipment (Router, Antenna, Radio AP)

Operation and maintenance of power farm and power supply

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science, Physics , 08/2021 University of Ilorin - Ilorin , Kwara

## CONTACT

**Address:** 3 Oliver Tambo street Asokoro , Federal Capital Territory , Abia State 900231

Phone: +2349036884342 Email: devbrymo@gmail.com

### SKILLS

- · CSS
- · HTML coding
- · Website optimisation
- WordPress
- Web development projects
- · React
- JavaScript
- GitHub
- Three.js
- Shopify
- · Bootstrap